吸血鬼日记 前情回顾
Previously on "The Vampire Diaries"...
达蒙死了
Damon is gone.
我要你催眠我 让我忘记我曾爱过他
I want you to compel me to forget that I ever loved him.
-达蒙萨瓦托尔是谁 -他就是个畜生
- Who is Damon Salvatore? - He's a monster.
要回家 我们就得利用一个古设备
To get home, we'll harness the power
来吸收日蚀的力量
of the eclipse using a mystical relic.
不
No.
我的妻子被吸血鬼杀了
Vampires murdered my wife.
我要靠他找出他的其他吸血鬼朋友
I'm gonna get him to name all his vampire buddies.
需要帮助吗
Need any help?
如果你心底还有一点点
If even just a small, little part of you
是想回来看我的话
came back to check on me,
那就留下来吧
then stay.
我过的不好 达蒙
Not doing so great, Damon.
我不知道该怎么办
I'm lost, brother.
说来话长 弟弟
It's kind of a long story, brother,
但是我还是回来了
but I'm back.
求你放我走
Please just let me go.
我知道这看起来有点血腥暴力
I know this may seem a little barbaric,
但是我保证 不会滥用私刑
but I promise you, it's nothing personal.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
我们可没有这么多时间来解释这个
It's a longer story than we have time for,
但是 相信我 你也不想过这样的生活
but... trust me... you don't want this life...
如果这还能叫做生活的话
If you can call it that.
再加把劲
All right. Come on.
快 快
Come on. Come on.
快
Come on.
怎么回事 怎么回事 啊
What's that? What is that? Aah!
到底是怎么了
What is happening? Aah!
吸血鬼
第六季  第六集
日记
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
-我也很想你 -难以置信
- I missed you, too, buddy. - I can't believe it.
翻译：小P Espionage Krystle Brian
我以为你走了
I thought you were gone.
你不会以为我死了的那种走吧
You didn't think I was gone gone, huh?
我发誓要给你永生的折磨
Promised you an eternity of misery.
校对：小P 香蕉奶昔
哈哈
Ha ha!
他回来了
He's back?
-怎么回来的 -我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
说实在的 他说达蒙回来了
Honestly, everything Stefan said
时轴：络睿   压制：hhjie   总监：络睿
之后的每句话我都心不在焉了
after, "Damon is back," Is kind of a blur.
邦妮呢
What about Bonnie?
她牺牲了自己 我才得以回来
She sacrificed herself so I can come back.
我不想其他人知道
I don't want anyone to know.
不可以再让大家都痛苦了
There's no sense making this harder
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
大家都够烦的了
than it already is.
那我们要怎么告诉其他人
What are we gonna tell people?
他说邦妮没和他在一起
He said that she wasn't over there.
那他是在哪里
Where is there, exactly?
-1994年的神秘瀑布镇 -我知道很难相信
- Mystic Falls, 1994? - I know.
女巫们结合她们的力量
A bunch of witches were gonna get together
创造了一个时空监狱
and create some space-time purgatory,
我也希望她们挑的时间能好一点
you'd think they'd pick a better year than
而不是选了科特柯本自杀的那年
the one that Kurt Cobain killed himself.
整件事情真是太折磨人了
Whole thing was just very depressing.
那你是怎么回来的
So how did you get back?
说来话长 我眼前闪过一大片闪光
Long story... big flash of light,
现在还有二十年的时差还没倒回来
two decades' worth of jet lag.
等回家了我再跟你说
I will explain all of my adventures
我的离奇遭遇 但是现在
in that flannel hellscape, but first,
我赶着去见个人
there's someone I got to go see.
我不想见到他
I don't want to see him.
我明白
I get it,
但是你现在就是这么想的 埃琳娜
but that's how you feel now, Elena.
如果你认为你有一点点的机会能见到
If you thought there was even a chance
达蒙的话 你是绝不会
you'd see Damon again, you would have never
叫我催眠你忘记你和他之间的事的
asked me to compel away your memories of loving him.
她做了什么
She did what?
她叫阿拉里克做的
She had Alaric do it.
-达蒙会杀了我的 -你又杀不死
- Damon is going to kill me. - You're unkillable.
这并不意味着他不会试试看
Doesn't mean he won't try.
你认为我见到他会怎么样
What do you think is gonna happen when I do see him?
我必须得去见她 斯特凡
I just need to see her, Stefan.
我们的眼神交汇 催眠就会失效
Our eyes will meet, fireworks will go off,
一切都会恢复正常
and the balance of nature will be restored.
她爱我
She loves me.
-他就是个神经失常的杀人狂 -你这么想是因为
- He's a psychotic killer. - You only feel that way
我把关于他的好的记忆都抹掉了
because I erased all the good parts.
我看不到他有什么好可以抵消掉他的坏
I don't see anything that could balance out the bad.
答应我 不要解除催眠
Promise me you won't lift the compulsion.
-答应我 -我不会的
- Promise me. - I won't, ok,
除非是你要求 好吗
not until you ask me to,
-谢谢 -但是 埃琳娜
- thank you. - But, Elena,
我希望你能叫我解除催眠
I hope you ask me.
我得走了 还得去医院值班
I have to go. I have a shift at the hospital.
-从什么时候开始你要值班了 -从达蒙回来那一刻开始
- Since when? - Since Damon came back
我会不顾一切地躲着他
and I'm trying desperately to avoid him.
好吧 如果你要躲着谁的话
Fine, but if you're avoiding people,
顺便也躲着乔吧
add Jo to your list.
那天晚上我试着催眠
I compelled her to forget our date
她忘了我们的约会 没用
the other night, and it didn't take.
没用是什么意思
What do you mean, it didn't take?
要不她就是服了马鞭草 要不然就是别的原因
Well, either she's on vervain or there's some other reason,
总而言之 我们催眠不了她
but she can't be compelled.
-你试试看能不能找到原因 -好
- So see if you can find out why. - Ok. Yeah. I will.
你会打电话给杰里米吗
Will you call Jeremy?
我得跟他说说邦妮的事
I had to tell him about Bonnie over the phone.
你也能想到他的反应了
You can imagine how that went.
-你要去哪 -要出去
- Where are you going? - Out.
你答应过我会帮我找到我的亲戚的
You promised me you'd help me track down my relatives.
晚点 好吗
Just... later, ok?
杰里米 你不能说了一句 扎克萨瓦托尔是你爸爸
Jeremy, you can't just say, "Zach Salvatore was your dad.
遗憾的是他死了 然后就出去吧
Too bad he's dead," And then, "Peace out."
现在我没时间帮你找亲戚
I can't do this right now.
是什么事这么紧急让你
What is so urgent to make you
终于舍得把屁股从沙发上挪开了
finally unglue your ass from the couch?
我知道不是学校的事 也不是工作
I know it's not school. It's not work.
如果是有关另一个女生的话 那我想先去洗个澡
If it's another girl, I'd shower first.
我只是想离开这里
I just need to get out of here.
特里普的跑腿仔回来了
Tripp's errand boy returns.
哦 我的错
Ooh, my bad.
没事 兄弟
Heh. That's all right, mate.
你靠过来一点
Just lean in,
然后我就可以自己喝了
and I'll take it right from the tap.
这个就不用了
I'll pass.
就这点
Yeah? Come on.
我得恢复体力 你才能帮我逃走
I'm gonna need my strength back for when you help me escape.
对不起 如果是斯特凡帮忙抓你的话 那我想你是罪有应得
Sorry. If Stefan turned you in, I'm guessing you deserved it.
什么时候斯特凡成了道德标杆了
When did Stefan's moral compass become the new true north?
不是他逃去一个
Wasn't he the one who scurried off
无名小镇吗
to some poxy, little town while he
他还让所有人以为
let everyone believe he was still
他还在努力找他哥哥
searching for his brother?
要我说 这可不是什么豪言壮举啊
Not exactly the hero move, if you ask me.
我还是认为把你关在这里
Still, I think the general population
大家的人身安全才更有保障
is safer with you in here.
好吧 可能你说得对
Yeah. Probably right,
除了埃琳娜
well, except for Elena...
斯特凡 卡罗琳 还有你
Stefan, Caroline, you.
你认为我把你知道吸血鬼的事
What do you think would happen if I
告诉你老板
were to tell your boss about known vampires
他会怎么做
and their groupies?
去萨凡纳这一趟就是在浪费汽油
Well, Savannah was a waste of gas.
有那么几个血袋 但是你跟我们说的房子
Minus a few blood bags, the house you told us about
是空的
was empty.
真奇怪 他们肯定是收到风提前逃走了
Odd. Must have smelled you coming.
幸好我遇到一个女生
Hmm, would have been a total bust,
她和你描述的一模一样
except I happened upon a girl
要不然这一趟就一无所获了
that fit the description that you gave me.
是在靠近惠特默尔学院抓到的
That was near Whitmore,
但是离你说的地方有50英里
500 miles from where you said she was gonna be.
-是艾薇吗 -就是她
- Is this Ivy? - That's the one.
我再给你一天时间想清楚
So I'm gonna give you today to conjure up
你的吸血鬼朋友们在哪
the location of your vampire friends,
要不然我可要带你去神秘瀑布镇
or you and I are gonna go sightseeing
走一趟了
in Mystic Falls.
你为什么不告诉我们
Why didn't you tell us Enzo has been
恩佐一直都被关着呢
locked up this whole time?
说真的 我不觉得有谁关心他
Honestly, I didn't know anybody was missing him.
-马特 -抱歉
- Matt! - I'm sorry.
我实在是搞不清楚现在我们喜欢的是谁
I was confused about which vampires we like
讨厌的又是谁
and which ones we don't.
那艾薇呢 她是不是也在那
Ok. Well, what about Ivy? Is she there, too?
特里普把她和另外两个吸血鬼载过边境了
Tripp drove her and two others across the border last night.
天哪
Oh, God.
那你知不知道特里普现在在哪
Well, do you know where Tripp is now?
他在跟另一条线索
He's running down another lead,
但是他没告诉我是什么线索
but he didn't tell me what it was.
你能去找一下是什么吗
Well, can you find out?
我们得弄清楚他的下一个目标是谁
We need to know who his next target is.
如果恩佐同意说的话 下个目标就是你们
If Enzo talks, it'll be you guys.
那是不可能的
Well, that's not going to happen
因为我们会把他救出来 是不是
because we're busting him out, right,
那样我才能臭骂这没用的家伙竟然被逮到了
if for no other reason than so I can kick his ass
然后再把他揍一顿
for getting caught in the first place.
你知不知道特里普
You have any idea how he even managed
是怎么抓到他的吗
to get his hands on it?
他才抓不到 是我抓的
He didn't. I turned him in.
谁
Who is it?
是我
Hey, it's me.
我有话要跟你说
I just wanted to talk.
现在我没空
I can't, not now.
我知道你为什么要这么做
Look. I know why you did what you did.
那都不是真的
It's not real.
你知道什么是真的吗 你对我的感觉就是真的
You know what's real? The way you felt for me.
你曾经跟我说这是你这辈子
You once told me that it was the most real thing
感受到的最真实的事了
you ever felt in your life.
-现在这些感觉都没了 -拜托 埃琳娜
- Those feelings are gone. - Oh, come on, Elena.
你也催眠过别人
You've compelled enough people to know
那只能掩盖真相
it's just a way of covering the truth,
无论你多想要掩盖真相
and no matter how badly you want it done,
谎言还是谎言
it doesn't make it any less of a lie,
你知道吗
you know?
我听到你的呼吸了
Oh, I hear you breathing.
你不知道我想听到你的呼吸想了多久
You have no idea how long I've wanted to hear you breathe.
开门吧 埃琳娜
Just open the door, Elena.
一切都会回归正轨的
Everything can go back to the way it was.
就
Just...
开门就好了 埃琳娜
Just open the door, Elena, please...
那你至少走开点
Or, at the very least, step aside
因为我准备破门而入了
because I'm gonna kick this door in.
惠特默尔学院
北部校区
真的吗 你真的跳窗逃走了
Seriously? You jumped out of a window?
如果被别人看到了怎么办
What if somebody saw you?
我知道 我知道 我很害怕 我也不知道怎么做
I know, I know. I panicked. I don't know.
他在那已经被困了好几个月了
Look. He's been trapped over there alone for months.
他就是想见见你
He just wants to see you.
我知道我应该有什么感觉
Look. I get how I'm supposed to feel,
但是我也感受到了我的真的感觉 我现在很开心
but I know how I actually feel, and I'm happy now.
如果我看到了他 然后我的感觉
What if I look at him and my old feelings
都冲破催眠重新回来了怎么办
break through the compulsion?
不会的 如果真的会
Well, they won't, but even if they did,
也不是一件坏事啊
is that such a bad thing?
是啊 我就像你一样重新开始了 好吗
Yeah. I started over just like you did, ok?
我为我自己 还有我的未来
I made a smart choice for myself
做出了明智的选择
and for my future.
斯特凡 我昨晚吻了利亚姆
Stefan, I kissed Liam last night.
噢 请忘记你告诉了我这个
Oh, please forget that you told me that
而且千万不要把这个告诉达蒙
and definitely do not tell Damon that.
因为他会杀了利亚姆的 是吗
Because he's gonna kill him, right,
就像他杀了我的弟弟一样
just like he killed my brother.
我是想说 因为他肯定会心碎的
I was gonna say because he'll be heartbroken.
听着 你想做什么呢
Listen. What do you want to do?
我是说 你最终还是得见他的
I mean, you have to see him eventually.
我知道 但是我就是没准备好
I know, but I just don't think
今天就见到他 好吗
eventually can be today, all right?
我没
I'm not...
我就是没 准备好
I'm just not... ready.
我要走了
I got to go.
- 埃琳娜  - 嘿
- Elena. - Hey.
我还以为你今天不会来的
I didn't think you were here today.
嗯 是啊 我改变了计划
Yeah. No. I changed my schedule around.
好吧 跟我来
Ok. Follow me.
在电脑中查找
吸血鬼
查找结果
查找中
在电脑中查找
未找到相关文件
神秘瀑布镇死亡案
莎拉 你在干嘛
Sarah, what are you doing?
我可以问你同样的问题
Could ask you the same question.
你不能来这儿
You can't be in here.
看你紧张的样子 要么你在下黄片
From the look on your face, either you're downloading porn
要么就是你也不该来这儿
or you're not supposed to be here, either.
你在特里普的办公室干嘛
What are you doing in Tripp's office?
你想要什么
What do you want?
一些以前住在这儿的人的信息
Information on some people who used to live here.
你知道塞尔瓦托家族的任何事情吗
You know anything about the Salvatores?
不太了解
Not really.
好吧 杰里米说 扎克·塞尔瓦托是我的爸爸
Well, according to Jeremy, Zach Salvatore was my dad.
都说他死于一次动物袭击
He supposedly died from an animal attack,
而且 碰巧的是 我妈妈也是死于动物袭击
and, coincidentally, so did my mom,
但是我关注好久了
but I've been paying attention.
我知道这种说法是什么意思
I know what that's code for,
而且你的老板似乎
and your boss seems to know a lot
对致命的野生动物非常了解 所以
about homicidal wildlife, so...
所以你认为闯进来看看是个好主意
So you thought breaking in here was a good idea.
我猜你也有这种想法
Guess we have that in common.
现在 要么你来帮我 要么当我告诉你老板
Now, either you help me or start coming up
你在偷查他资料的时候 想想找个什么借口好吧
with a good lie when I tell your boss you were snooping.
动物袭击案件的档案 都在那边
Animal attacks are filed over there.
萨尔茨曼教授
Professor Saltzman.
怎么 不能催眠你自己成为一个博士吗
What, couldn't compel yourself a Ph.D.?
-不敢相信你居然回来了 -是的哥回来了
- I can't believe you're back. - I am. Heh.
-那么 你到底怎么样了 -嗯 让我们看看吧 里克
- So... how the hell are you? - Well, let's see, Ric.
我从某种旧式口袋状的小宇宙中
I clawed my way
连滚带爬逃出来
out of some retro pocket universe,
却发现我还要催眠自己
only to find that I needed to compel myself
换个身份
a new change of clothes
因为这个反魔法罩
because this antimagic hamster ball
一直在阻止我回来
is keeping me from going home,
然后我又发现我最好的朋友
and then I find out that my best friend,
却对此无动于衷
rather than doing anything about it,
反而在这种时候
decided that it was the best use of his time
催眠我美丽又可爱的女朋友
to compel my beautiful and lovely girlfriend
让她忘记曾经爱过我
to forget that she ever loved me.
哼 我真的很好 里克 谢谢你的关心
Heh. I'm great, Ric. Thanks for asking.
听着 达蒙
Look, Damon.
我知道的 她如果没有我 就会一团糟 好吗
I know she was a train wreck without me, ok,
可是清除所有记忆 真的至于吗
but a full mind erase, seriously?
她实在太爱你了 这份爱让她痛不欲生
She loved you too much, and it was killing her.
嗯 我感到很荣幸
Well, I'm flattered,
但是我回来了
but I'm back.
所以让我们
So let's get this uncompulsion
把她的记忆恢复好吗
on the books, huh?
好的 只要埃琳娜告诉我她想这样就行
Fine, as soon as Elena tells me that what she wants.
嗯 那么问题来了
Right. Here's the thing.
如果她记不起为什么要恢复记忆
She's not gonna want to be uncompelled
那她就不会想恢复记忆了
if she can't remember why she'd want to be uncompelled.
嗯嗯 鸡生蛋蛋生鸡的循环
Mm-hmm. Chicken, egg.
我知道 很遗憾
I know, and I'm sorry.
遗憾 她连见都不想见我了 里克
Sorry? She won't even see me, Ric.
我明白 达蒙 但她现在很开心
I get it, Damon, but she's happy,
所以除非她要求我这么做
and I'm not gonna take that away from her
否则我不会给她恢复记忆的
until she asks me to.
我不是不想埃琳娜开心
It's not like I don't want Elena to be happy.
我只是想要她和我一起开心
I just want her to be happy with me.
好吧
Right.
看 恩佐并不是很小心
Look. Enzo wasn't being careful.
特里普最终会抓住他的
Tripp would've caught him eventually,
那就意味着我们全都会有危险
and that meant danger for all of us.
真对 所以你交出了恩佐
Right. So you handed Enzo over
这样猎人就不会追杀我们了 现在
so we wouldn't be targeted, and now
你又要救恩佐 猎人就又无法追杀我们了
you're rescuing him so we won't be targeted.
你真是天才
Way to go.
好吧 我以为特里普会杀了他
Well, I thought Tripp was gonna kill him.
我没想到他会为了得到信息 而让他活着
I didn't think he was gonna keep him alive for information.
噢 好吧 这样听起来
Oh, well, in that case, sounds like you
你还真是个实在人啊
were just being practical.
-所以你也出卖了艾薇 是吧 -什么
- So did you rat out Ivy, too? - What?
不是吗 你已经不想再和她交易
Well, you didn't want to deal with her anymore.
你想要她消失 她还真消失了
You wanted her gone, and now she is.
你知道么
You know what?
你真该对特里普说谢谢
You really should write Tripp a thank-you note.
慢着慢着 恩佐转化了艾薇 对吧
Hold on a second. Enzo turns Ivy, right?
一个猎人杀了她 然后我倒成了坏人咯
A hunter kills her, and yet I'm the bad guy?
我不是那种 威胁要出卖别的吸血鬼
I'm not the one threatening to turn in
好来保住自己的人
other vampires to save his own skin.
唯一出卖吸血鬼给猎人的人
The only one who's turned in other vampires
就是你 斯特凡
is you, Stephan.
所以你才过来帮忙
That's why you're helping...
你害达蒙的朋友被抓 你心虚了
Guilt for getting Damon's friend captured.
呵呵 达蒙是我哥 我第一个抛弃他
Yeah. Damon is my brother, and I gave up on him first.
恩佐没有
Enzo didn't.
所以如果救他的二货朋友
So if rescuing his idiot friend
在某种程度上可以补偿他
is gonna somehow make it up to him,
那这件事就该由我来做
that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
很好 你觉悟了啊
Great. Good for you.
你想好该怎么补偿我的时候
Let me know when you figure out how you're
跟我说一声啊
gonna make everything up to me.
我们进去看看
Let's get in there.
他到底在哪儿
Well, where the hell is he?
我喜欢你的手镯 什么材料做的
I like your bracelet. What is it made of?
不知道
No idea.
既然你在这儿 有些事情我能问问你的看法吗
While you're here, can I get your opinion on something?
当然 好啊
Sure. Yeah.
一个女病人
Female patient...
头部钝力创伤 大量内出血
Blunt-force trauma to the head, massive internal hemorrhaging,
多处骨折
multiple bone fractures.
她是麦田迷宫的受害者
She was a victim at the corn maze.
可她在哪儿
Where is she?
可能在上大一的文学课
Probably freshman lit.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我也不明白
Neither do I.
瞧 这个病人其实一直没入院治疗
See, the patient was never admitted,
即使受了这么严重的伤
even with such extensive injuries.
利亚姆说你当场给她紧急治疗了
Liam said you treated her at the scene.
对于一个只读了半学期医学预科的人来说
That's a pretty good save for someone
真是了不起
with half a semester of pre-med.
好吧 我觉得他们
Yeah. I think they were exaggerating
夸大了她的伤情
how bad off she was.
当时天很暗 而且 到处是血
It was dark, and, yeah, there was a lot of blood.
别解释了 我知道阿拉里克的情况 我知道你的情况
Don't. I know what Alaric is. I know what you are.
如果再有血袋消失
If any more blood bags go missing,
我知道要找谁
I know who to come to.
某人做得真绝啊
Well, somebody was thorough.
一张达蒙的照片都没有
No pictures of Damon anywhere.
噢
Ohh...
你这样会吓死个人啊
It's kind of creepy, you just standing there
站那儿一动不动 一声不吭
all hulky and brooding.
你倒先说起来了 跟踪我姐姐的怪蜀黍
Says the freak who's stalking my sister.
严格来说 我是躺在这儿等
Technically, I'm lying in wait.
邦妮为什么没回来
Why didn't Bonnie come back?
她为什么没回来
Why didn't she come back?
因为她不在那儿
Because she wasn't there.
就我在那儿
It was just me.
你知道我还在给她充话费
You know I paid her cell bill
这样我就能每天打她电话
so I could call her phone and hear her say
听她说同样的六个字吗
the same 6 words every day?
听起来不错 我也会打一个
Sounds good. I'll give it a call.
为什么 她讨厌你
Why? She hated you.
邦妮没和我一起在那儿 杰里米
Bonnie wasn't there with me, Jeremy,
因为她获得了安息
because she found peace.
她找到了更好的地方
She's in a better place.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know?
一方面我不相信你
Besides not believing that you closed
能够在没有急救装备的情况下
a penetrating abdominal trauma
缝合一个贯穿腹部的创伤
without so much as a first aid kit?
另外我非常确信你不是在我的咖啡里找甜叶菊
Pretty sure you weren't looking for stevia in my coffee.
对于阿拉里克 我不是百分百的确定
With Alaric, I wasn't 100% certain
他想要催眠我 但是接着我想起
he tried to compel me, but then I remembered
我的爱情一直在走狗屎运
I have really crappy luck in my love life.
所以必须的 我那火辣的恋人老师
So of course my hot, new teacher crush
肯定是个吸血鬼
would be a vampire.
-那么你又是什么 -我很忙
- So then what are you? - Busy.
如果你想要继续呆在这儿
If you want to stick around, there's food trays
三楼有脏盘子 去刷干净
on the third floor that need clearing.
就这样么 你打算让我留在这儿
That's it? You're gonna let me stay?
你救了那个女孩 而不是吸她的血
You saved that girl instead of feeding on her.
-我看你还是挺好的 -对于这件事
- That's good enough for me. - You're not even afraid,
你甚至都不害怕 不担心
not ever fazed, for that matter.
只有一种人 能够在不需要马鞭草的情况下
There's only one thing that can resist compulsion
抵抗吸血鬼的催眠 那就是女巫
without needing vervain, and that's a witch.
你是个女巫
You're a witch.
咱们做个交易怎么样
How about I make a deal with you?
你不要问关于我的问题
You don't ask questions about me,
我也不会问关于你的问题
and I won't ask questions about you.
成交
Deal.
噢 而且你可以告诉阿拉里克
Oh, and you can tell Alaric,
如果他想避免一段凌乱的感情
if he wants to avoid a complicated relationship,
他不需要催眠任何人
he doesn't have to hide behind compulsion to do it.
可能我没在这儿长大是件好事情
Maybe it was a good thing I didn't grow up here.
那么你从哪儿来呢
So where do you come from?
我每年都住在不同的地方
Give me the year, and I'll give you
寄养在不同的家庭
the town and foster home.
噢 真好
Oh, good.
好像知道里面有什么
Wonder what's in here.
锁住了
It's locked.
锁住了意味着很重要
Locked means important.
-嘿 卡罗 你找到他了吗 -没有 恩佐不在这儿
- Hey, Care, did you get him? - No. Enzo is not here.
除了这个明显的地点之外
Any idea where Tripp might have taken him
特里普还会把他带到哪去呢
besides the very obvious one?
等等 我看个东西
Hang on. Let me see that.
卡罗琳 福布斯
卡罗琳 我们有新麻烦了
Caroline, we have another problem.
特里普收着艾薇的手机
Tripp... Has Ivy's phone.
然后呢 我是说这家伙是个杀人狂
And? I mean, the guy is a murderer.
顺手牵羊对他来说小菜一碟
Petty theft isn't much of a stretch.
但你的名字在
Yeah, but your name is at the top
最近通话记录的顶部
of the recent dialed list.
噢天哪 他知道我是什么了
Oh, my God, he knows what I am.
我猜他知道怎么找你了
I'm guessing he knows where to find you.
是邦尼 请给我留言
It's Bonnie. Leave me a message.
就这样
That's it?
你的语音信息就这样吗 开什么玩笑
That's your outgoing message? Really?
我是说 我主动找寻你的声音的时候
I mean, the one time I'm actively seeking
我只找到了这个
the sound of your voice, that's all I get.
很好 嗯
Perfect. Hmm.
不管怎么样 我在你的屋子里
Anyway, I'm in your room,
实际没听起来那么奇怪
which is a lot less weird than it sounds.
我只是想说
I just wanted to say that
因为你为我做了那么多
because of what you did for me,
今天我找到了埃琳娜
today is the day that I get to see Elena.
所以 谢谢
So thank you,
而且 我很抱歉
and I'm sorry.
除了这个我不知道要说什么了
Other than that, I don't know what to say
或者说除了这个我应该说什么
or what I'm supposed to say except that,
听起来好像是绝不可能
defying all possible global scenarios,
但 我有一点想念你了
I might miss you a little bit.
噢 嘿 我得走了
Ooh, hey, I got to go.
所以你没有忘记我的电话号码么 这个开端不错
So you didn't forget my number. That's a good start.
是的 我猜我要按达蒙的按钮
Yeah. I figured I'd press the Damon button
看看会发生什么
and see what happened.
-现在怎么了 -我不知道
- And what is happening? - I don't know.
我都不知道我在做什么
I don't even know what I'm doing.
我只是
I just...
我觉得我们应该面对面地谈一次
I'm thinking we should meet face to face.
我不能一直逃避你
I can't run from you forever.
所以来我的宿舍吧
So come by my dorm?
好 好 我会到这儿的 那儿
Yeah. Yeah. I'll be here. There.
我会去那儿的 一定 马上就去
I'll be there, absolutely, in a bit.
-马上见 -好的
- See you in a little bit. - Ok.
你还挺快的
Well, that was fast.
啊
Agh!
你是谁
Who are you?
呃
Uh...
达蒙
Damon?
埃琳娜 冷静
Elena, calm down.
你只要去找卡罗琳 然后到达老米勒路
Just find Caroline and get to old Miller road.
我们会把他带回来
We'll get him back.
我和埃琳娜进行了一段非常有趣的对话
I had an interesting conversation with Elena.
是啊 我想听到全部内容 只是不是现在
Yeah, and I want to hear all about it, just not right now.
急什么 紧急超自然课程么
What's the rush, occult studies emergency?
是的 我需要去某些地方
Yeah. I have someplace I need to be.
所以如果你不介意
So if you don't mind...
你为什么不催眠我让路
Why don't you just compel me out of the way?
你看 你不觉得已经到了
Look. Don't you think it's about time
我们互相坦白的时候了吗
we level with each other?
好吧 这样怎么样
Ok. How's this?
我最好的朋友 他刚刚复活
My best friend, he just came back from the dead,
但是我现在要赶在
but now I have to save him
他被一个吸血鬼猎手载着
from a vampire hunter before he's driven
越过反魔法界限 并再次被杀掉之前救他
across an antimagic border and killed again.
所以现在给你一点建议
So here's some friendly advice.
也许离我远点
It's probably a good idea to stay
对你来说更好
as far away from me as possible.
呃
Uh...
-早安啊 亲爱的 -恩佐
- Morning, sunshine. - Enzo?
嗯 这还真是怀念这个啊
Well, this brings back memories.
我很高兴你想办法回来了 伙计
I'm glad you found a way back, mate.
虽然恐怕这是一次短暂的相逢
Afraid it's gonna be a short reunion, through.
我们要去神秘瀑布镇
We're headed to Mystic Falls, known for its bridges;
那个以桥和复古小镇魔法而出名的地方
quaint, small-town charm;
还有一个大大的吸血鬼控制问题
and a really big vampire bug zapper.
斯特凡本来可以告诉我镇子里有一个吸血鬼猎人的
Stefan could've told me there was a hunter in town.
也许他忘记了
It probably slipped his mind because he's
因为我重新被关押是他的责任
responsible for my return to incarceration.
他为什么要这么做
Why would he do that?
也许是嫉妒我的口音
Probably jealous of my accent.
嗯 也许他这么做是因为
Eh, maybe he did it because I killed
我杀了他的新女朋友
his new girlfriend.
嗯 这就说得通了
Yeah. That'll do it.
抱歉 妈妈
Sorry, mom.
伊莲娜在参加 疯狂汽车迷节目
Elena is auditioning for "Top Gear."
嗯 没事
Yeah. Ok.
拜
Bye.
所以 我妈妈正在关闭13号线路
So my mom is shutting down route 13.
军队还会再回来
Tripp will have to double back,
然后只有两条穿过界线的路径
and there's only two other ways across the border.
你对轮胎有偏好吗 前面还是后面
Do you have a tire preference... front, back?
没有 好的
No? Ok.
这样做好像自然了点
I think this sells a spinout.
你觉得呢 埃琳娜
What do you think? Elena?
我想要回我的记忆
I want my memories back.
等等 什么
Wait. What?
我决定了
I made up my mind.
如果这次达蒙没死
If Damon survives this,
我就要阿拉里克解除掉催眠
then I want Alaric to uncompel me.
我是说 我不能想象爱过他
I mean, I can't imagine ever loving him.
我也不能为了回避事实
I also can't ignore
而只忽略掉我不喜欢的部分
the parts I don't like just to avoid the truth.
我的意思是 如果我只知道一半的故事
I mean, how would I make any decisions
我怎么能做出任何决定
if I only know half the story?
你不需要拆掉引擎
You don't have to take apart the whole engine.
我们只需要引诱特里普进来 这样就能救他们
We just need to lure Tripp in so we can grab them.
你知道的 这不是你的错
You know, it's not your fault.
这就是
Pretty much is.
听着 你不是唯一一个放弃了的
Look. You're not the only one who gave up.
过去四个月的每一秒
Every second for the last 4 months,
我想到的只有
all I could think about was when I'm gonna get
我什么时候能再喝到血
my next sip of blood, when am I gonna
我什么时候能弄糟一切 伤害到某些人
screw up and hurt somebody,
我复活过来
why did I come back to life
就是要做这样的事
just to be this thing,
我一度猎杀吸血鬼
that I used to hunt vampires
突然 我成了吸血鬼的一员
and suddenly, I was one.
寻找达蒙是唯一
Searching for Damon was the only thing
能让我不再想这些的事
that could take my mind off of it,
但是我基本上要把任务当做让我分心的东西
but I was basically going through the motions
因为 说实话 斯特凡
as a distraction because, honestly, Stefan,
我也会放弃的
I'd given up, too.
来了
There.
那就是他  你要待在车里
That's him. You should stay in the car.
-他知道你长得什么样子 -他认为我是他那边的
- He knows what you look like. - He thinks I'm on his side.
是啊 但是恩佐可能出卖了你
Yeah, unless Enzo told him different.
去告诉埃琳娜他在这里
Go tell Elena he's here.
晚上好
Evening.
要带我的朋友去单身聚会
Tried to get my buddy to a bachelor party,
我们的车不走了
and our car just stopped.
你能帮帮我们么
You think you can help us out?
嗯 我对车一窍不通
Uh, don't know anything about cars.
是的
Yeah.
嗯 也许你能载我一段
Well, maybe you could give us a ride, then.
那是谁
Who's that?
里克 他肯定是有计划
Ric. He's up to something.
肯定是好事 他还欠我一个人情
Better be good. Bastard owes me.
抱歉 有点赶时间
Sorry. In a bit of a hurry.
是啊 我们也是
Yeah. So are we.
啊
Uh!
啊 噢
Uh! Ooh!
噢
Oh!
啊 啊 啊 啊
Uh! Uh! Ugh! Agh!
斯特凡
Stefan.
斯特凡 怎么了
Stefan, what's happening?
达蒙和阿拉里克越过了边境
Damon and Alaric are across the border.
我得挂了
I got to go.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
啊 啊啊
Agh! Ugh! Aagh!
啊
Ah!
我回来可不是为了这样子
I came back for this?
看着自己慢慢死去
Consumption wasn't much fun
并不是很有趣
the first time around, either.
没事了 我在这儿
It's ok. I'm here.
怎么
How?
像个疯狂的跟踪者一样跟踪你
Followed you like a crazy stalker,
可不是什么好差事
not one of my finer moments.
不不 抓住他
No, no. Get him.
你一定要让我回到边境那边去
You have to get me across the border.
它在消除魔力 我会死掉的
It's stripping away the magic. I'll die.
如果我动了你 你会死的
You'll die if I move you.
我需要止血
I have to stop the bleeding.
划破了你下面的主动脉
Nicked your descending aorta.
我知道 这就是会弄死我的东西
I know. That's what killed me.
你没有让我回来 是吧
You didn't have me back then, did you,
并且你也没有止血纱布
and you didn't have hemostatic gauze.
起来 快点 起来
Get up. Come on. Get up.
啊
Ugh!
怎么了
What's happening?
你还清醒着吗
You still with me?
我在处理这个伤口的时候
While I'm sealing this wound,
我想要你想一想
I want you to think about how you tried
你当时多么努力的迷惑学校里最聪明的女生
to compel one of the smartest women on campus
让她忘记她和你的约会
to forget about her date with you,
那次我单打独斗救了几十个生命的约会
the date where I single-handedly saved
而我甚至连妆都没花
dozens of lives without smearing my makeup.
阿拉里克 坚持住
Alaric? Hang on.
别走
Stay with me.
拜托 心快跳起来啊
Come on. Gonna get that heart pumping.
你还没对我说你想说的话呢
You don't get to have the last word with me.
阿拉里克
Alaric!
别走
Stay with me.
拜托
Come on.
啊
Ah...
有  有 有点不对劲
So... so... Something is wrong.
-别动 -不
- Don't move. - No.
有点不对劲
Something is wrong.
我不应该活下来
I'm not supposed to be alive.
你也没有理由死掉
There's no reason you shouldn't be.
我封住了伤口
I sealed the wound.
我们现在得送你去医院
We just have to get you to the hospital.
嗯 我会告诉他
Yeah. I'll tell her.
字幕
Thanks.
我刚刚在9号路线
I was just at route 9,
出现了一次撞击 但是他们不在那儿
and there was a crash, but they weren't there.
是的 我知道
Yeah. I know.
他们离开那儿了
They had to get out of there.
发生什么了
What happened?
斯特凡说
Stefan said that...
什么 卡罗琳 什么
What, Caroline? What?
阿拉里克跨过了边境
Alaric crossed the border,
但是乔在那边 她救了他
but Jo was there, and she saved him.
所以他没事
So he's ok.
这说明他还好 是吧
That means he's ok, right?
是的 伊莲娜 他没事
Yeah, Elena. He's ok.
那你为什么是那种表情的
Then why do you have that look on your face?
发生什么了 卡罗琳
What happened, Caroline?
所有魔法都消失了
All the magic stripped away,
但是乔在他死之前救了他
but Jo saved him just before he died.
什么
What?
我听不懂你在说什么 卡罗琳
I don't know what that means, Caroline.
阿拉里克不再是吸血鬼了 埃琳娜
Alaric is not a vampire anymore, Elena.
他已经是个普通人了
He's human.
谢谢你载我一程
Thanks for the ride. Yeah.
我觉得我只是省去了
I thought I'd save you the trouble
你再偷一辆车的麻烦
of having to boost another car.
真好笑
That was almost funny.
不过你还可以在搞笑些的 多诺万
Hope for you yet, Donovan.
如果我告诉你我了解你的家族
If I told you I knew about your family,
你能接受一个小小的友好的建议吗
promise to take a little friendly advice?
等等
Hang on.
你了解我的家族
You know who my family is?
我翻阅了关于这个镇上
Read any history book
创始成员的所有历史书
about the town's founding members.
住在这间屋里的人
The guys that live in this house
是塞尔瓦托兄弟 达蒙和斯特凡
are Damon and Stefan Salvatore.
为什么你要现在告诉我这些
Why are you just telling me this now?
因为
Because...
他们是吸血鬼 不论他们去哪
They're vampires, and wherever they go,
总会带来死亡和痛苦
death and pain always follow.
所以如果你要找关于家族的事情
So if you're looking for family,
在这你是不会有发现的
you're not gonna find it here.
就当帮你自己个忙
Do yourself a favor and get
离这越远越好吧
as far away from this place as you can.
给点力啊
Come on!
不 真该死
No. Damn it!
杰
Jer...
我一直尝试着注销掉邦妮的电话
I keep trying to cancel Bonnie's phone,
但是没有她的pin码 我办不到
but I can't without her pin.
为什么我记不起她的pin码
Why can't I remember her pin?
啊
Uh!
啊 啊
Uh! Uh!
放开我 放开我
Get off! Get off!
嘿 没事了 不 不是的
Hey, it's ok. No, it's not!
她不在了
She's gone.
邦妮不在了
Bonnie is gone.
乔是个好保姆 感觉怎么样
Jo is a keeper. How does it feel?
噢 真疼啊
Oh, it hurts a lot.
在神秘瀑布没有一个吸血鬼可以帮着去治疗你
Well, it's too bad there aren't any vampires in Mystic Falls
真是太糟糕了
to help heal you.
好吧 我觉得他们给我滴注了吗啡
Well, I think they got me on a morphine drip.
这是接来下最好的事了
It's the next best thing.
埃琳娜 我很抱歉
Elena, I'm so sorry.
不 阿拉里克
No. No, Alaric.
看到你没事我很开心
I'm just glad that you're ok.
我是说 直到一个小时前
I mean, up until an hour ago,
我都不想恢复我的记忆
I didn't even want my memories to return.
是我做了那个失去他们的决定
I was the one who made the choice to lose them.
现在我必须面对
Now I have to live with the fact
无法把他们再还给我的现实
that you can't give them back to me.
我知道你有多讨厌成为一个吸血鬼
I know how much you hated being a vampire.
所以我很开心我们中的一个人达成了我们大家的心愿
So I'm just glad one of us got what we wanted.
那你想要的到底是什么呢
And what is it that you want?
能够看着达蒙的眼睛
To be able to look Damon in the eye,
知道所有我想知道
knowing all that I know
和我不想知道的一切
and all that I don't, and...
还有看看我对他有什么感觉
See how I feel about him.
我想相信我的感觉
I want to trust how I feel.
我希望你能行 祝你好运 好吗
I hope that you can. Good luck, ok?
这家医院烂透了
This hospital sucks.
我不敢相信有人能活着出院
I can't believe anyone actually makes it out alive.
一般没人活着出去
They usually don't.
我尽快把你转移到惠特默尔去
I'm having you transferred to Whitmore ASAP.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我只是做我该做的事
Just doing my job.
嘿
Hey...
你做的可不止这些
You did more than that.
你让我重获新生
You gave me back my life.
多谢
Thank you.
我当时只有一步之遥 一步之遥啊
I was this close, this close.
我知道 我很抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
哦 我懂了 每个人都感到抱歉
Oh, I got it. Everybody is sorry.
你很抱歉你对我绝望
You're sorry you gave up on me,
你很抱歉把恩佐出卖给了猎人
sorry you turned Enzo in to that hunter guy.
里克对那次催眠感到抱歉
Ric is sorry for the compulsion.
我相信如果埃琳娜能记起所有
I'm sure if Elena could remember anything,
她也会感到抱歉的
she'd be sorry, too.
你要理解这对她来说有多艰难
You got to understand how hard it was for her.
听到这些我都不耐烦了
I am so tired of hearing about how hard it was for her.
我也很艰难啊
It was hard for me, as well.
至少你知道你有家可回
At least you knew you had a home to come back to.
她一无所有了 对她来说 你已经消失了
She didn't have anything. To her, you were just gone.
那就假设我消失了吧
Guess I still am.
里克说自从她忘记我之后过的很快乐
Ric said she's happy without me since she's erased me.
你知道吗 我不想她快乐
You know what? I don't want her to be happy.
我想让她变得和我一样悲惨
I want her to be miserable just like I am.
说完了吗
You done?
完了 不错
- Yeah. I'm done. - Good.
不要再拖时间了
Now quit stalling.
有个女孩你要去见见
There's a girl you need to go see.
如果它没效果怎么办
What if it doesn't work?
如果我们所拥有的不够强大
What if what we had isn't strong enough
去打破催眠怎么办
to break the compulsion?
那你是只想坐在这而不去解决事情吗
You're not gonna find out just sitting there, are you?
我还是呆在这里吧
Here goes everything.
嗨
Hey.
那么
So...
我是斯特凡道歉之旅上
Am I your last stop
的最后一站吗
on the Stefan Salvatore apology tour?
我们能不能把这事忘记
Could we just get past this, please?
-我一直在尝试 -听着 卡罗琳
- I'm trying to. - Look, Caroline.
你想让我做什么 嗯
What do you want me to do, huh?
不要再让我瞎想了 告诉我我该做什么
Stop making me guess and tell me
能让我们做回朋友
so we can go back to being friends again.
好吧 现在是这样的 斯特凡
Yeah. Well, that's the thing, Stefan.
经历过这些之后
After all of this, I...
我不想再和你做朋友了
I don't want to be friends anymore.